<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>A Tester&#39;s Adventure</title>
    <link>https://anamariapopa.netlify.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content on A Tester&#39;s Adventure</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 18:10:14 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://anamariapopa.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Another way of using Test Sphere</title>
      <link>https://anamariapopa.netlify.app/article/test-sphere/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 18:10:14 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anamariapopa.netlify.app/article/test-sphere/</guid>
      <description>Test Sphere is a card deck about (obviously) testing from Ministry of Testing. The cards are treating different aspects, being divided in 5 categories:
 Heuristics, Techniques, Feelings, Quality aspects, Patterns.  Each card presents a testing concept and 3 directions to tackle the concept.
It is usually used to create a testing approach, for risk storming or in scrum events such as planning (to look at the next increment in a different way) or retrospectives (especially the cards in Feelings category).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Mary Catherine Bateson - How to become a systems thinker</title>
      <link>https://anamariapopa.netlify.app/quote/systems-thinker/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2021 14:40:32 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anamariapopa.netlify.app/quote/systems-thinker/</guid>
      <description>Great majority of Americans still believe that &amp;ldquo;Positive feedback&amp;rdquo; is when someone pats you on the back and says you did a good job. What positive feedback is saying is, do more of the same. So, if what you’re doing is taking heroin or quarreling with your neighbor, this is just going to lead to trouble. Negative feedback corrects what you’re doing. It’s not somebody saying, &amp;ldquo;That was a lousy speech.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KPIs and Metrics in Testing</title>
      <link>https://anamariapopa.netlify.app/article/kpi-and-metrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 18:10:14 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anamariapopa.netlify.app/article/kpi-and-metrics/</guid>
      <description>There is a question that keeps bugging me for a while: How to measure testing, what metrics should I take into consideration?
Starting with the failed experience of reporting some indicators that were looking good for the management, but didn’t really help me or the end customers, I asked myself: is there any point in measuring some indicators for quality? Why should I even bother to look at some numbers if they don’t matter that much?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>State of Testing Survey</title>
      <link>https://anamariapopa.netlify.app/link/state-of-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 10:45:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anamariapopa.netlify.app/link/state-of-testing/</guid>
      <description>Fellow testers, take a few minutes to answer the survey</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://anamariapopa.netlify.app/status/testers-pub/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 10:45:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anamariapopa.netlify.app/status/testers-pub/</guid>
      <description>Tester&amp;rsquo;s Pub at Yonder
Testers&#39; Pub este un eveniment de suflet pentru mine deoarece am fost de față când a luat naștere ideea și am participat într-o măsură mai mică sau mai mare la fiecare ediție. Ediția asta trecem în online. La fel ca mai toate evenimentele de acest gen. Chiar dacă s-a schimbat contextul, scopul Testers&#39; Pub rămâne același: sa adune oamenii pasionați de testare, sa facem share de informații, să învățăm împreună, participanți, cei care prezintă sau organizatori.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://anamariapopa.netlify.app/status/domains-of-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2020 10:45:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anamariapopa.netlify.app/status/domains-of-work/</guid>
      <description>Domains of work and Testing
Trying to locate yourself in a domain of work helps you understand better your role, which is the position on the market for the product you are testing and which are your client&amp;rsquo;s expectations. James Bach defines, as an example, five domains of technical work in this link{:target=&amp;quot;_blank&amp;quot;}
article
The fact that I can find myself in multiple domains at different moments, demonstrates the complexity of testing activity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Agile Testing: A Practical Guide for Testers and Agile Teams</title>
      <link>https://anamariapopa.netlify.app/article/agile-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 18:10:14 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anamariapopa.netlify.app/article/agile-testing/</guid>
      <description>I received the book a couple of years ago from my Scrum Master (thanks Johan!). He was strongly recommending it for the entire team. So, another book suited not only for testers but for the entire team, especially in an agile environment.
Nowadays, when everyone talks about Modern Testing and TestOps, this book might seem outdated but reading it can help familiarize with terms, practices and roles in agile. Before learning how to run, you have to know how to walk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To all the Good Evil Testers out there: Dear Evil Tester</title>
      <link>https://anamariapopa.netlify.app/article/evil-tester/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 18:10:14 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anamariapopa.netlify.app/article/evil-tester/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Dear Evil Tester&amp;rdquo; is a book from Yonder testing bookshelf. This is how I got the chance to read it. It is written in Alan Richardson&amp;rsquo;s unique style.
I don&amp;rsquo;t think you will find another testing book that will make you laugh out loud as this one (unless it&amp;rsquo;s so bad that it&amp;rsquo;s funny).
No alt text provided for this image It includes 3 parts. The first one contains answers to the letters received by the author at &amp;ldquo;The Testing Planet&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In order to truly understand anything, you have to explore it</title>
      <link>https://anamariapopa.netlify.app/article/explore-it-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 18:10:14 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anamariapopa.netlify.app/article/explore-it-1/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Explore It! Reduce the Risk and Increase Confidence with Exploratory Testing&amp;rdquo; is the second book in my list. Part of Pragmatic Bookshelf, reading it made me change my testing mindset, improve my skills and helped me discover new and useful heuristics. Elisabeth Hendrickson&amp;rsquo;s book is full of stories and practical example and should be kept on any tester&amp;rsquo;s desk in order to be consulted at need.
No alt text provided for this image This is not a book that you can read while laying in the bed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More than just a testing book: Lessons Learned in Software Testing: A Context Driven Approach</title>
      <link>https://anamariapopa.netlify.app/article/lessons-learned/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 18:10:14 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anamariapopa.netlify.app/article/lessons-learned/</guid>
      <description>A list of books is just a list unless you&amp;rsquo;ve read the books, you processed the information and you have an opinion about it. So I&amp;rsquo;m going to write a few thoughts about the books that I mentioned in my previous post.
I will start with &amp;ldquo;Lessons Learned in Software Testing: A Context Driven Approach&amp;rdquo; by Cem Kaner, James Bach and Bret Pettichord. It is a compilation of testing related stories, experience gathered by the authors along many years, summarized in 293 lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://anamariapopa.netlify.app/status/testing-one-on-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2020 10:45:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anamariapopa.netlify.app/status/testing-one-on-one/</guid>
      <description>Testing and Frustrations
Listening to this episode in Testing One on One podcast made me thing about the strong feelings (I will not use the word frustration) I have about testing. For example, why most of the people that want to start a career in IT think they should begin with testing, &amp;ldquo;because it&amp;rsquo;s easier&amp;rdquo;. Or why testing/testers are not getting the same importance as developing/developers. After all, we all are in the same boat and should have the same goal: happy customers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://anamariapopa.netlify.app/status/test-automation-univ/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2020 10:45:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anamariapopa.netlify.app/status/test-automation-univ/</guid>
      <description>Resources on Test Automation University
It is difficult to learn a new technology when you don&amp;rsquo;t know the prerequisites. You know the destination but you don&amp;rsquo;t know the way. People from Test Automation University suggest the learning path for multiple topics. You can also find the related courses, provided by important names in testing field. Of course, a few hours course won&amp;rsquo;t make you a master and you will have to dig a little deeper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://anamariapopa.netlify.app/status/online-test-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 10:45:44 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anamariapopa.netlify.app/status/online-test-conference/</guid>
      <description>A Modern Tester With Scrum Master Hat
Check out my presentation at OnlineTestConf on how a Scrum Master role can be picked up by a tester: A Modern Tester With Scrum Master Hat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books about testing</title>
      <link>https://anamariapopa.netlify.app/status/testing-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 18:01:26 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anamariapopa.netlify.app/status/testing-books/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a list of books that I find useful for testers:
 Lessons Learned in Software Testing Explore It! Agile Testing Dear Evil Tester  Reading them helps a lot in creating the mindset, improving your vocabulary so you can better express your view when needed and you can learn from other people&amp;rsquo;s experience</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
